dorcousa.com 2018-11-26

# Dorco USA – Privacy Policy

Dorco® USA understands that your privacy is important to you. We sincerely appreciate your trust in us to keep your information safe. The main goal in collecting your personal information is to provide an efficient and accurate ecommerce experience.

We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, billing and mailing addresses and email addresses. We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other manner. We use your personal information to process your online order and provide you with the best ecommerce experience possible. We may also use your information to improve our website's content and layout, improve our inventory and for our marketing and advertising efforts. All emails, newsletters and other forms of communication from this site allow you to opt out from further communication at any time.

Our website may also use cookies and tracking technology. Cookies and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system. This helps in tracking the number of visitors to the website and understanding how visitors use our web site. Cookies can also help customize the website for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Naturally populated cookies and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

Our website incorporates physical and electronic procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") for all financial transactions through this website. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online.

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when:

(1) permitted or required by law  
(2) to protect against or prevent potential fraud or unauthorized transactions  
(3) investigating fraud, which has already taken place

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at our sole discretion. Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted on this website page.
